[
  {
	"id": 1,
	"question": "How many Dragon Balls are there?",
	"answer": "7",
	"category": "Anime",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 2,
	"question": "In Spy x Family, what is the special ability of Anya Forger, the adopted daughter of Loid Forger?",
	"answer": "Telepathy",
	"category": "Anime",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 3,
	"question": "In Attack on Titan, what is the name of the gear do the soldiers use to fight Titans?",
	"answer": "Omni-Directional Mobility Gear (ODM Gear)",
	"category": "Anime",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 4,
	"question": "In Jujutsu Kaisen, what does Yuji Itadori swallow to become the host of a powerful curse?",
	"answer": "Sukuna’s Finger",
	"category": "Anime",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 5,
	"question": "In My Hero Academia, what is a hero’s ability called?",
	"answer": "Quirk",
	"category": "Anime",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 6,
	"question": "In Pokémon, what does Pikachu evolve into?",
	"answer": "Raichu",
	"category": "Anime",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 7,
	"question": "Where is the location of 'Vinland', a historical land featured in Vinland Saga? Name the country or region.",
	"answer": "Canada (specifically Newfoundland)",
	"category": "Anime",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 8,
	"question": "How many episodes does One Piece have?",
	"answer": "1121",
	"category": "Anime",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 9,
	"question": "In JoJo’s Bizarre Adventure, what is the name of the supernatural manifestation of a person’s fighting spirit that grants them unique powers?",
	"answer": "Stand",
	"category": "Anime",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 10,
	"question": "What is the name of the talking black cat in Sailor Moon?",
	"answer": "Luna",
	"category": "Anime",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 11,
	"question": "In Dune, what is the name of the valuable substance that can only be found on the desert planet Arrakis?",
	"answer": "The spice melange",
	"category": "Science Fiction",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 12,
	"question": "In The Matrix, what is the name of the real-world city where humans are hiding from the machines?",
	"answer": "Zion",
	"category": "Science Fiction",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 13,
	"question": "What classical problem in physics lends its name to a popular science fiction novel that has had a recent Netflix adaptation?",
	"answer": "Three Body Problem",
	"category": "Science Fiction",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 14,
	"question": "What is the name of the monster in Frankenstein?",
	"answer": "It has no name",
	"category": "Science Fiction",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 15,
	"question": "In 2001: A Space Odyssey, what is the mysterious object discovered on the Moon called?",
	"answer": "The Monolith",
	"category": "Science Fiction",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 16,
	"question": "In Ready Player One, what is the name of the virtual reality world created by James Halliday?",
	"answer": "The OASIS",
	"category": "Science Fiction",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 17,
	"question": "In which star system does the majority of the Avatar films take place in?",
	"answer": "Alpha Centauri",
	"category": "Science Fiction",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 18,
	"question": "In Star Trek, who was the first captain of the USS Enterprise?",
	"answer": "Captain Christopher Pike",
	"category": "Science Fiction",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 19,
	"question": "Tom Cruise starred in which 2014 action movie involving time travel?",
	"answer": "Edge of Tomorrow",
	"category": "Science Fiction",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 20,
	"question": "In Back to the Future, which fictional device is essential for time travel?",
	"answer": "Flux Capacitor",
	"category": "Science Fiction",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 21,
	"question": "When was the first moon landing? (closest year wins)",
	"answer": "1962",
	"category": "Important Dates",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 22,
	"question": "Which year did the Three Kingdom Era of China start? (closest year wins)",
	"Answer": "222",
	"category": "Important Dates",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 23,
	"question": "Which month is named in honour of Emperor Gaius Octavius?",
	"answer": "August",
	"category": "Important Dates",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 24,
	"question": "Which century was the America's discovered by Europeans?",
	"answer": "11th",
	"category": "Important Dates",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 25,
	"question": "When was the Dominion of Canada invaded by its southern American neighbours? (closest year wins)",
	"answer": "1812",
	"category": "Important Dates",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 26,
	"question": "Where was the Hanging Gardens of the the seven wonders?",
	"answer": "Babylon",
	"category": "Places",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 27,
	"question": "Between the provinces of Upper Canada and Lower Canada which was further north?",
	"answer": "Lower Canada",
	"category": "Places",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 28,
	"question": "Which modern nation was Archduke Ferdinand assassinated in?",
	"answer": "Serbia",
	"category": "Places",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 29,
	"question": "Where was the historic capital of Japan before it was moved to Tokyo?",
	"answer": "Kyoto",
	"category": "Places",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 30,
	"question": "Which state was famously sold to the United States in 1867?",
	"answer": "Alaska",
	"category": "Places",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 31,
	"question": "Who was the last undisputed king of France?",
	"answer": "Louis Philippe I",
	"category": "Historic Figures",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 32,
	"question": "Which British general famously lead the British-Canadian army in the Burning of Washington?",
	"answer": "Robert Ross",
	"category": "Historic Figures",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 33,
	"question": "Who was the British Prime Minister before Winston Churchill?",
	"answer": "Neville Chamberlain (also accept Clement Attlee)",
	"category": "Historic Figures",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 34,
	"question": "Who was the first woman to fly cross the Atlantic?",
	"answer": "Amelia Earhart",
	"category": "Historic Figures",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 35,
	"question": "Who lead the 1453 Siege of Constantinople?",
	"answer": "Sultan Mehmed II",
	"category": "Historic Figures",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 36,
	"question": "Which US president is famously depicted crossing the Delaware?",
	"answer": "LeBron James",
	"category": "Historic Figures",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 37,
	"question": "Who are the only Canadian father/son duo to serve as prime ministers?",
	"answer": "Pierre Elliot and Justin Trudeau",
	"category": "Historic Figures",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 38,
	"question": "Who was the third astronaut on the moon?",
	"answer": "Charles P. Conrad",
	"category": "Historic Figures",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 39,
	"question": "Which modern artist is famously known for the words 'But we friends tho'?",
	"answer": "Tyla",
	"category": "Historic Figures",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 40,
	"question": "Which Egyptian noble is known for having died young?",
	"answer": "King Tut",
	"category": "Historic Figures",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 41,
	"question": "How would you declare a variable x to be 10, in Python?",
	"answer": "x = 10",
	"category": "DSA",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 42,
	"question": "What is the difference between a for loop and a while loop?",
	"answer": "For for loops, number of iterations are known will for while loops, they are not",
	"category": "DSA",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 43,
	"question": "How many edges are in a tree with n nodes?",
	"answer": "n-1",
	"category": "DSA",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 44,
	"question": "What does BFS stand for?",
	"answer": "Breadth First Search",
	"category": "DSA",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 45,
	"question": "What is the time complexity of bubble sort?",
	"answer": "O(n^2)",
	"category": "DSA",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 46,
	"question": "What happens during a DFS when you reach a node which has already been visited previously?",
	"answer": "it is a cycle",
	"category": "DSA",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 47,
	"question": "What is the time complexity of accessing an element in an array?",
	"answer": "O(1)",
	"category": "DSA",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 48,
	"question": "What is the value of Integer.MAX_VALUE (in java) or INT_MAX (in C++)",
	"answer": "2^31 - 1",
	"category": "DSA",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 49,
	"question": "What is a naive implementation colloquially known as?",
	"answer": "Brute Force",
	"category": "DSA",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 50,
	"question": "What does (5 | 6) evaluate to?",
	"answer": 7,
	"category": "DSA",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 51,
	"question": "What does this expression produce, (2 << 4)",
	"answer": 32,
	"category": "DSA",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 52,
	"question": "Name one site where tech companies host their online assessments (OAs)",
	"answer": "HackerRank, CodeSignal, Codility, etc.",
	"category": "DSA",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 53,
	"question": "How many LeetCode coins do you get by solving the daily problem?",
	"answer": "10",
	"category": "DSA",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 54,
	"question": "What was the language, Racket’s original name?",
	"answer": "PLT Scheme",
	"category": "DSA",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 55,
	"question": "When was C++ invented?",
	"answer": 1979,
	"category": "DSA",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 56,
	"question": "What approach is famous for solving the knapsack problem?",
	"answer": "DP",
	"category": "DSA",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 57,
	"question": "There is an algorithm called SPFA in graph theory, what is its full name?",
	"answer": "Shortest Path Faster Algorithm",
	"category": "DSA",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 58,
	"question": "What is the runtime of binary search?",
	"answer": "O(logn) ",
	"category": "DSA",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 59,
	"question": "How many nodes are in a perfect binary tree of height n?",
	"answer": "2^n - 1",
	"category": "DSA",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 60,
	"question": "What data structure is first in first out?",
	"answer": "queue",
	"category": "DSA",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 61,
	"question": "Which song by Benny Blanco has the most streams on Spotify?",
	"answer": "Eastside",
	"category": "Music",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 62,
	"question": "Which song is commonly associated with videos of vehicles drifting?",
	"answer": "Deja Vu",
	"category": "Music",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 63,
	"question": "Which music video (excluding Baby Shark) has the most views on YouTube?",
	"answer": "Despacito",
	"category": "Music",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 64,
	"question": "Which rapper wrote the song 'Gang Related'?",
	"answer": "Logic",
	"category": "Music",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 65,
	"question": "Which K-Pop group released the album 'Armageddon'?",
	"answer": "Aespa",
	"category": "Music",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 66,
	"question": "Which heavy metal singer notoriously bit the head off a live bat?",
	"answer": "Ozzy Osbourne",
	"category": "Music",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 67,
	"question": "How many Ed Sheeran albums are named after mathematical symbols?",
	"answer": "5",
	"category": "Music",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 68,
	"question": "What is the net worth of Taylor Swift's cat? (Closest answer wins)",
	"answer": "$97 million",
	"category": "Music",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 69,
	"question": "What is Kendrick Lamar's last name? (It is not Lamar)",
	"answer": "Duckworth",
	"category": "Music",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 70,
	"question": "Who wrote the song \"The Man Who Sold The World\"?",
	"answer": "David Bowie",
	"category": "Music",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 71,
	"question": "In the English Civil War, who led the Parliamentarian army and was later proclaimed Lord Protector of the Commonwealth of England, Scotland, and Ireland?",
	"answer": "Oliver Cromwell",
	"category": "History",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 72,
	"question": "In what year did Thomas Paine publish his pamphlet titled Common Sense, which garnered popular support for the independence movement of the Thirteen Colonies from the United Kingdom?",
	"answer": "1776",
	"category": "History",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 73,
	"question": "Leif Erikson was credited with the discovery of Vinland (now known as North America), what was his father's name?",
	"answer": "Erik the Red\n(also accept Erik Thorvaldsson or just Erik)",
	"category": "History",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 74,
	"question": "In the 2024 TV series Shōgun (将軍), Yoshii Toranaga (吉井 虎永) went on to unite the entirety of Japan after the end of the series finale, establishing the longest-lasting shogunate in history. What was the name of his historical counterpart?",
	"answer": "Tokugawa Ieyasu\n(also accept 徳川 家康, Matsudaira Takechiyo, 松平 竹千代, Matsudaira Ieyasu, 松平 家康, Matsudaira Motoyasu, or 松平 元康)",
	"category": "History",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 75,
	"question": "Which country contains the launch site that the first artificial satellite, Sputnik 1, was launched from?",
	"answer": "Gagarin's Start\n(also accept Baikonur Cosmodrome)",
	"category": "History",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 76,
	"question": "The pharaohs' burial sites of the New Kingdom of Ancient Egypt between the Eighteenth Dynasty and the Twentieth Dynasty were noted for their departure from the traditional pyramid style. Where are these tombs located?",
	"answer": "The Valley of Kings\n(also accept the Theban Necropolis)",
	"category": "History",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 77,
	"question": "Who was the popular Zulu king who reformed the kingdom and expanded its reach in the 19th century?",
	"answer": "Shaka\n(also accept Sigidi)",
	"category": "History",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 78,
	"question": "France was the kingdom of the longest reigning sovereign in history. What was his name?",
	"answer": "Louis XIV\n(also accept Louis the Great, Louis le Grand, the Sun King, or le Roi Soleil)",
	"category": "History",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 79,
	"question": "What is the name of the pre-Columbian South American empire that is located in modern-day Chile and Peru?",
	"answer": "Inca Empire\n(also accepts Tawantinsuyu)",
	"category": "History",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 80,
	"question": "Who was the captain of the first ship to cross the Antarctic Circle?",
	"answer": "Capt. James Cook",
	"category": "History",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 81,
	"question": "What was the name of Kitchener, before 1916?",
	"answer": "Berlin",
	"category": "Waterloo Trivia",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 82,
	"question": "How much did it cost to build E7? (closest answer wins)",
	"answer": "88 million",
	"category": "Waterloo Trivia",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 83,
	"question": "What company known for making corporate cell phones is a product of Waterloo students?",
	"answer": "BlackBerry ",
	"category": "Waterloo Trivia",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 84,
	"question": "What color tie do students in the Math faculty wear, and perform a dance in?",
	"answer": "Pink",
	"category": "Waterloo Trivia",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 85,
	"question": "Which three cities make up the 'Tri-City'?",
	"answer": "Kitchener, Waterloo, and Cambridge",
	"category": "Waterloo Trivia",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 86,
	"question": "Which restaurant in the UW Plaza is infamous for its 'number of lines'?",
	"answer": "Lazeez",
	"category": "Waterloo Trivia",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 87,
	"question": "Which chess-based movie is famously filmed in Waterloo?",
	"answer": "The Queen’s Gambit",
	"category": "Waterloo Trivia",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 88,
	"question": "Which handsome online personality appeared at Waterloo REV last week?",
	"answer": "CityBoyJJ ",
	"category": "Waterloo Trivia",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 89,
	"question": "How many quiet study rooms are there in DC?",
	"answer": "Five (don’t forget the Staebler Insurance room!)",
	"category": "Waterloo Trivia",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 90,
	"question": "What is the style of architecture of MC?",
	"answer": "Brutalism ",
	"category": "Waterloo Trivia",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 91,
	"question": "What is the name of the company that manages the public scooters around campus?",
	"answer": "Neuron",
	"category": "Waterloo Trivia",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 92,
	"question": "What are the names of the four towers in Rez-One?",
	"answer": "Ferguson, Blair, Hespeller, Elora ",
	"category": "Waterloo Trivia",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 93,
	"question": "What is the name of the road that goes all around campus?",
	"answer": "Ring Road ",
	"category": "Waterloo Trivia",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 94,
	"question": "What is the name of the Waterloo professor who won the Nobel prize in 2018? ",
	"answer": "Donna Strickland ",
	"category": "Waterloo Trivia",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 95,
	"question": "What year was Waterloo founded?",
	"answer": "1957 ",
	"category": "Waterloo Trivia",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 96,
	"question": "What is the oldest building on campus? ",
	"answer": "Grad house ",
	"category": "Waterloo Trivia",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 97,
	"question": "Which League of Legends champion has the ultimate 'Last Breath'?",
	"answer": "Yasuo ",
	"category": "Waterloo Trivia",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 98,
	"question": "What is the longest recorded time that someone has ever gone without showering? (closest answer wins)",
	"answer": "60 years",
	"category": "Waterloo Trivia",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 99,
	"question": "What is Vivek Goel’s home address?",
	"answer": "382 Rosella Blvd",
	"category": "Waterloo Trivia",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 100,
	"question": "Who is DC named after?",
	"answer": "William G. David",
	"category": "Waterloo Trivia",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 101,
    "question": "What is the capital of Australia?",
    "answer": "Canberra",
    "category": "World Capitals",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 102,
    "question": "What is the capital of Iceland?",
    "answer": "Reykjavik",
    "category": "World Capitals",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 103,
    "question": "What is the capital of Brazil?",
    "answer": "Brasília",
    "category": "World Capitals",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 104,
    "question": "What is the capital of Uraguay?",
    "answer": "Montevideo",
    "category": "World Capitals",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 105,
    "question": "What is the capital of Egypt?",
    "answer": "Cairo",
    "category": "World Capitals",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 106,
    "question": "What is the capital of Argentina?",
    "answer": "Buenos Aires",
    "category": "World Capitals",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 107,
    "question": "What is the capital of Serbia?",
    "answer": "Belgrade",
    "category": "World Capitals",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 108,
    "question": "What is the capital of India?",
    "answer": "New Delhi",
    "category": "World Capitals",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 109,
    "question": "What is the capital of Burkina Faso?",
    "answer": "Ouagadougou",
    "category": "World Capitals",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 110,
    "question": "What is the capital of Oman?",
    "answer": "Muscat",
    "category": "World Capitals",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 111,
    "question": "Who is the CEO of Tesla and SpaceX?",
    "answer": "Elon Musk",
    "category": "Tech CEOs",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 112,
    "question": "Who is the CEO of Amazon?",
    "answer": "Andy Jassy",
    "category": "Tech CEOs",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 113,
    "question": "Who is the CEO of Apple?",
    "answer": "Tim Cook",
    "category": "Tech CEOs",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 114,
    "question": "Who is the CEO of Meta Platforms (formerly Facebook)?",
    "answer": "Mark Zuckerberg",
    "category": "Tech CEOs",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 115,
    "question": "Who is the CEO of Alphabet (Google's parent company)?",
    "answer": "Sundar Pichai",
    "category": "Tech CEOs",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 116,
    "question": "Who is the CEO of Microsoft?",
    "answer": "Satya Nadella",
    "category": "Tech CEOs",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 117,
    "question": "Who is the CEO of Twitter (X)?",
    "answer": "Linda Yaccarino",
    "category": "Tech CEOs",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 118,
    "question": "Who is the CEO of Netflix?",
    "answer": "Ted Sarandos",
    "category": "Tech CEOs",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 119,
    "question": "Who is the CEO of Nvidia?",
    "answer": "Jensen Huang",
    "category": "Tech CEOs",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 120,
    "question": "Who is the CEO of Oracle?",
    "answer": "Safra Catz",
    "category": "Tech CEOs",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 121,
    "question": "Song #1",
    "answer": "Father Stretch My Hands Pt.2",
    "category": "Name the Song",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 122,
    "question": "Song #2",
    "answer": "Blinding Lights",
    "category": "Name the Song",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 123,
    "question": "Song #3",
    "answer": "Butter",
    "category": "Name the Song",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 124,
    "question": "Song #4",
    "answer": "Apple",
    "category": "Name the Song",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 125,
    "question": "Song #5",
    "answer": "Thriller",
    "category": "Name the Song",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 126,
    "question": "Song #6",
    "answer": "Thrift Shop",
    "category": "Name the Song",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 127,
    "question": "Song #7",
    "answer": "Old Town Road",
    "category": "Name the Song",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 128,
    "question": "Song #8",
    "answer": "Fortnight",
    "category": "Name the Song",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 129,
    "question": "Song #9",
    "answer": "One Dance",
    "category": "Name the Song",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 130,
    "question": "Song #10",
    "answer": "YMCA",
    "category": "Name the Song",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 131,
    "question": "Which city hosted the 1986 Summer Olympics?",
    "answer": "Athens",
    "category": "Olympics",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 132,
    "question": "Who is the most decorated Olympian of all time?",
    "answer": "Michael Phelps",
    "category": "Olympics",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 133,
    "question": "In which year did the first modern Olympics take place?",
    "answer": "1896",
    "category": "Olympics",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 134,
    "question": "Which country has won the most Olympic medals in history?",
    "answer": "United States",
    "category": "Olympics",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 135,
    "question": "In which city were the 2020 Summer Olympics held?",
    "answer": "Tokyo",
    "category": "Olympics",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 136,
    "question": "Who was the first woman to win five individual Olympic gold medals in gymnastics?",
    "answer": "Nadia Comăneci",
    "category": "Olympics",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 137,
    "question": "How many points did Steph Curry get in the 2024 Finals against France? (closest answer wins)",
    "answer": "24",
    "category": "Olympics",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 138,
    "question": "Which city hosted the 2012 Summer Olympics?",
    "answer": "London",
    "category": "Olympics",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 139,
    "question": "Which female gymnast won gold for all-around in 2020?",
    "answer": "Suni Lee",
    "category": "Olympics",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 140,
    "question": "Which country hosted the Winter Olympics in 2010?",
    "answer": "Canada",
    "category": "Olympics",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 141,
    "question": "Who are Simba’s best friends?",
    "answer": "Timon and Pumbaa",
    "category": "Disney Movies",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 142,
    "question": "What is the name of the reindeer in Frozen?",
    "answer": "Sven",
    "category": "Disney Movies",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 143,
    "question": "What object does Ariel use to comb her hair?",
    "answer": "A fork",
    "category": "Disney Movies",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 144,
    "question": "What color dress is most closely associated with Belle?",
    "answer": "Yellowt",
    "category": "Disney Movies",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 145,
    "question": "What was Aladdin’s first wish?",
    "answer": "To become a prince",
    "category": "Disney Movies",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 146,
    "question": "What species of animal is Moana’s companion on the boat?",
    "answer": "Chicken",
    "category": "Disney Movies",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 147,
    "question": "What are the new emotions introduced in Inside Out 2?",
    "answer": "Anxiety, Embarrassment, Ennui, and Envy",
    "category": "Disney Movies",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 148,
    "question": "What is the name of Mulan’s dragon?",
    "answer": "Mushu",
    "category": "Disney Movies",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 149,
    "question": "What is the name of the prince in 'Sleeping Beauty'?",
    "answer": "Prince Phillip",
    "category": "Disney Movies",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 150,
    "question": "In the hit movie Encanto, which character do the others refuse to talk about?",
    "answer": "Bruno",
    "category": "Disney Movies",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 151,
    "question": "Who was the first Prime Minister of Canada?",
    "answer": "Sir John A. Macdonald",
    "category": "Canadian History",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 152,
    "question": "In which year did Canada become a country?",
    "answer": "1867",
    "category": "Canadian History",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 153,
    "question": "Who is known as the 'Father of Medicare' in Canada?",
    "answer": "Tommy Douglas",
    "category": "Canadian History",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 154,
    "question": "What year did women in Canada gain the right to vote in federal elections?",
    "answer": "1918",
    "category": "Canadian History",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 155,
    "question": "What is the name of Canada's national police force?",
    "answer": "Royal Canadian Mounted Police (RCMP)",
    "category": "Canadian History",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 156,
    "question": "Who was the Canadian Prime Minister during World War II?",
    "answer": "William Lyon Mackenzie King",
    "category": "Canadian History",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 157,
    "question": "Which province was the last to join Canada?",
    "answer": "Newfoundland and Labrador",
    "category": "Canadian History",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 158,
    "question": "In which year did Canada officially adopt its flag, the Maple Leaf?",
    "answer": "1965",
    "category": "Canadian History",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 159,
    "question": "What is the name of the first female Prime Minister of Canada?",
    "answer": "Kim Campbell",
    "category": "Canadian History",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 160,
    "question": "Who was the Canadian Prime Minister during the Great Depression?",
    "answer": "R.B. Bennett",
    "category": "Canadian History",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 161,
    "question": "Which celebrity starred in the movie Titanic?",
    "answer": "Leonardo DiCaprio",
    "category": "Celebrities",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 162,
    "question": "Who two rappers beefed near the beginning of the year?",
    "Answer": "Kendrick Lamar and Drake",
    "category": "Celebrities",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 163,
    "question": "Which celebrity is known as the Queen of Pop?",
    "answer": "Madonna",
    "category": "Celebrities",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 164,
    "question": "Which celebrity starred in the movie The Pursuit of Happyness?",
    "answer": "Will Smith",
    "category": "Celebrities",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 165,
    "question": "Who is the music producer most recently arrested for a string of criminal charges?",
    "answer": "Sean Combs (Diddy is also accepted)",
    "category": "Celebrities",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 166,
    "question": "Which actor is most famously associated with Scientology?",
    "answer": "Tom Cruise",
    "category": "Celebrities",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 167,
    "question": "Which celebrity most famously took a dump on their ex’s bed?",
    "answer": "Amber Heard",
    "category": "Celebrities",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 168,
    "question": "Which celebrity won an Oscar for the movie 'La La Land'?",
    "answer": "Emma Stone",
    "category": "Celebrities",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 169,
    "question": "Which celebrity is known for his portrayal of the Joker in 'The Dark Knight'?",
    "answer": "Heath Ledger",
    "category": "Celebrities",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 170,
    "question": "Which celebrity starred in 'Wonder Woman'?",
    "answer": "Gal Gadot",
    "category": "Celebrities",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 171,
	"question": "Name the Greek myth which Hadestown is based off",
	"answer": "Orpheus and Eurydice",
	"category": "Mythology",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 172,
	"question": "Name the hero in Japanese mythology that was born from a peach and fights ogres",
	"answer": "Momotarō",
	"category": "Mythology",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 173,
	"question": "Name the hero in Celtic mythology that wields the weapon Gáe Bulg",
	"answer": "Cú Chulainn",
	"category": "Mythology",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 174,
	"question": "In the myth of Eros and Psyche, what is the first trial that Psyche is given by Aphrodite?",
	"answer": "To sort a pile of seeds and beans into seperate piles by dawn",
	"category": "Mythology",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 175,
	"question": "In Mycenean Greece, who was the head of the Pantheon?",
	"answer": "Poseidon",
	"category": "Mythology",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 176,
	"question": "Dionysus is known as the god of wine (drunk). What was his predecessor, Orphic Dionysus, known as?",
	"answer": "A god of death and rebirth",
	"category": "Mythology",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 177,
	"question": "Name the character in Greek mythology who falls in love with his own face",
	"answer": "Narcissus",
	"category": "Mythology",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 178,
	"question": "In Chinese mythology, there were once 10 suns. Name the archer that shoots down 9 of the 10 suns",
	"answer": "Hou Yi",
	"category": "Mythology",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 179,
	"question": "What is the name of the book that is a collection of prose and poems describing the myths and history of Ireland?",
	"answer": "The Book of Invasions (Lebor Gabála Érenn)",
	"category": "Mythology",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 180,
	"question": "Name the two gods in Sumerian mythology that competed to create humanity",
	"answer": "Enki and Ninmah",
	"category": "Mythology",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 181,
	"question": "Give the course name for CS 343.",
	"answer": "Concurrent and Parallel Programming",
	"category": "UW Course Codes",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 182,
	"question": "Give the course name for CS 371.",
	"answer": "Introduction to Computational Mathematics",
	"category": "UW Course Codes",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 183,
	"question": "Give the course name for FINE 130.",
	"answer": "Introduction to Digital Imaging",
	"category": "UW Course Codes",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 184,
	"question": "Give the course name for PHYS 175.",
	"answer": "Introduction to the Universe",
	"category": "UW Course Codes",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 185,
	"question": "Give the course name for ENGL 101B.",
	"answer": "Introduction to Rhetorical Studies",
	"category": "UW Course Codes",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 186,
	"question": "Give the course code for the course \"Calculus 4\"",
	"answer": "AMATH 231",
	"category": "UW Course Codes",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 187,
	"question": "Give the course code for the course \"Compiler Construction\"",
	"answer": "CS 444",
	"category": "UW Course Codes",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 188,
	"question": "Give the course code for the course \"Introduction to Combinatorics (Advanced Level)\"",
	"answer": "MATH 249",
	"category": "UW Course Codes",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 189,
	"question": "Give the course code for the course \"Elementary German 1\"",
	"answer": "GER 101",
	"category": "UW Course Codes",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
	"id": 190,
	"question": "Give the course code for the course \"Introduction to Actuarial Practice\"",
	"answer": "MTHEL 131",
	"category": "UW Course Codes",
	"img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 191,
    "question": "What is the largest planet in our solar system?",
    "answer": "Jupiter",
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 192,
    "question": "Which planet is closest to the Sun?",
    "answer": "Mercury",
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 193,
    "question": "What is the name of the galaxy that contains our solar system?",
    "answer": "Milky Way",
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 194,
    "question": "What is the second smallest planet in our solar system?",
    "answer": "Mars",
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 195,
    "question": "What is the hottest planet in our solar system?",
    "answer": "Venus",
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 196,
    "question": "What is the name of the largest moon of Saturn?",
    "answer": "Titan",
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 197,
    "question": "What is the term for a star that has collapsed under its own gravity?",
    "answer": "Black hole",
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 198,
    "question": "Which planet in our solar system is known for its prominent ring system?",
    "answer": "Saturn",
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 199,
    "question": "What type of star is the Sun?",
    "answer": "Yellow dwarf (G-type main-sequence star)",
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 200,
    "question": "What is the term for the boundary around a black hole from which nothing can escape?",
    "answer": "Event horizon",
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 201,
    "question": "Which planet is known as the Morning Star or Evening Star?",
    "answer": "Venus",
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 202,
    "question": "What is the name of the closest star to Earth, other than the Sun?",
    "answer": "Proxima Centauri",
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 203,
    "question": "Which planet has the longest day (the time it takes to rotate once on its axis)?",
    "answer": "Venus",
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 204,
    "question": "What are comets mostly made of?",
    "answer": "Ice and dust",
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 205,
    "question": "Which dwarf planet is located in the asteroid belt between Mars and Jupiter?",
    "answer": "Ceres",
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 206,
    "question": "What is the term for a rocky object that enters Earth's atmosphere and burns up?",
    "answer": "Meteor",
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 207,
    "question": "What is the name of the first artificial satellite to be launched into space?",
    "answer": "Sputnik 1",
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 208,
    "question": "Which planet is known for having the Great Red Spot, a giant storm?",
    "answer": "Jupiter",
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 209,
    "question": "What is the most common type of galaxy in the universe?",
    "answer": "Elliptical galaxy",
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "img": "N/A"
  },
  {
    "id": 210,
    "question": "Which planet has the largest volcano in the solar system, named Olympus Mons?",
    "answer": "Mars",
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "img": "N/A"
  }
]
